OK, so now we will see the new concept called branching.
OK.
So let me tell you one scenario.
To understand why you're branching is necessary.
OK, so now get X and get demo, other two people working from different time jobs and corroborating
each other with the help of Get Hub Central Depository.
OK.
So now these guys are concentrating on test, gives us development.
So management decided to make some modifications on FRIM itself.
OK.
To make it more optimizer able are to introduce some new futures.
So they want to implement and enhance this framework to the next level.
So they have hired one architect maybe in both places.
And their job is to concentrate on framework components building, not on test cases.
OK.
These two guys are continuing the test gives this development for their regular deliverables.
But these architects have to now focus on the project structure, like introducing a new FUT. like Dustin
G.
Maven.
Are they want to drive the whole project from page object.
So they want to make many changes.
OK.
But when these guys started putting the actual code framework fails, obviously these groups will start
fail, isn't it.
Now in start off for data driven framework.
If these guys are trying to implement base object, they will change some configuration files in the
framework.
Right.
If the genes test, cases will fail.
OK.
So they need at least one month to come up with a new framework.
But in that one month, these test cases will not run because of these guys changes.
OK.
Because they're making changes component by component.
But these test cases are necessarily to run on every day basis.
OK.
They have to learn on an everyday basis just because of some deliverable commitments.
In that situation, we will take a branch, OK?
Just as you make three.
OK.
Three is a mustard branch.
From that master brand, we will take one more branch and some branch and that sub branch will actually
have the same core of what you have taken from or the general branch.
OK, master is our root branch.
So from our.
Let's take one branch and we will continue to work.
Architects basically can continue to work on this branch.
OK.
So all that development, whatever they are making, they do on the branch.
So in this vein, they are not.
That's in the master branch.
OK, Master Branch will continue to serve a regression.
This gets us on daily basis at the same time.
These guys have taken one more branch guard developed branch.
You could name it with anyone, but nonstandard people use to develop.
If it is a second branch after master.
So they develop branch.
They're developing this stuff again, the same way.
If was an architect, how to catch up with this look, he will actually pull the devil branch in start
off Master Branch again, sort of master.
These guys will invoke and develop and they complete.
So after one month.
Once they realized that this branch is fully ready and executes all our test cases, they simply meant
that they will branch into the actual master branch after thorough testing, making sure this band is
not breaking, they will melt entire branch into the master branch in this way.
At the end, people all will start using master bands with the latest changes done by architect.
But that happens only after a few days.
Right.
Because they have to start working and make some changes.
So this is the concept.
Now we will see how to take the branches and how to work on need.
And finally, how do Misty's branches work?
We have taken into our action, master.
That's the agenda for this lecture.
All right.
So right now I am in Get Demel.
I will go back to my time in front.
Let me go to any project so that we can dig the branch from there.
OK.
So right now, I made this project live in.
So this guy have to pick a brains because new architect Jarrin into the team.
OK.
This is Asian time, John.
When we say good them more, it's Asians.
Gays, OK, just for practice.
Just funny.
Not really time feel.
I am talking about this Joan time, John.
And that time, Joan, instead of confusing you between good demo and good stuff, I'm putting in this
terminology so that you'll remember.
OK.
There's nothing more than that.
So if you want to take a branch, if you want to cut a branch from this or you repository, we just
down here.
So that is a command to do that with get branch.
Hyphen.
Get take out.
OK.
Generally, we say take out the stuff, right?
Take out the brand, but create a new one when you want to create a new one.
Then you have to go.
Hyphen B, hyphen B stands for Creating New Branch.
OK.
You can get the same thing from this comment.
Basic good comments.
You can go through four master.
Here itself, you have good brands.
Is it missing here?
OK.
I think yeah, here it is.
Yeah.
Same thing, get take out hyphen B stands for Brand Name and you have to give the specific brands.
What do you want to create?
So here I will create the Willow branch.
So when you hit it that now it will create one more.
It klop is actually as one more quarter repository but it named it as the devil a branch so that you
can switch to that developed branch and you can work on died of that specific branch.
And once it is done you can mess that in.
Do what, actual masterbrand so that you know you are not disturbing that regular deliverables by taking
and adding separate branches.
So you don't end up.
It clearly says that switched to the new branch devil.
OK.
So if you want to know what branch I'm currently in, just two wide confusion.
You can type get branch and he can enter.
It will tell you that there are totally two branches in.
You get a good demo project and right now you are on develop branch.
OK.
This is what it is saying.
That's the way you're trying as a start.
OK.
So automatically when you switch to that there will a branch.
And when you go to you want to get demo, you want a glimpse.
Also will shift.
Just click on this and you will see that it shifts to develop branch.
And now you'll start making changes, whatever the changes to make.
You will not disturb those in the branch.
OK.
So now I'll I'll start playing it on adding few apps.
So let's assume that architect is in the art of genius, right?
No, I'm from for example, I'm just blindly giving in sort of to this.
I create three dust and they'll say two Android apps.
Even that STPI a test instead of two, I will add one more test.
So I'm making some random changes here.
You see that three test cases out here and AP along.
So we have three test cases, but in master there are only two.
And here that are two.
Right.
I allowed one book.
New Ireland could treat us here, treat us here, three dates here.
Perfect.
Now, let's assume that the architect, how enough changes.
But he had to push his score to report because there is one more architect working in American time
zone and he has to pull his latest corps to work on that.
Well, a branch, OK.
There are two people working on it.
So he can he did not ah, he could not keep that in his local.
He has to push the court on daily basis.
So you're know.
Right.
How to do all this fast.
We will have that for our entire project of staging because we are already on Dola brands here now.
So why do they want operations to perform here?
Will point to develop only until unless you switch to master.
Each and every command you provide here will apply to this develop brains only.
So I'm reading I'm adding them to stating first.
OK.
And then we will come in.
And then we will push the cord.
What happens then?
So to get status.
To see what all the firefighter.
Yes.
That's DARPA selenium.
Why not IBM?
IBM is not at it, OK?
I think we have not saved.
But we've saved now.
And you'll say good status.
And now IBM.
OK.
Let me do it.
Add.
OK.
That's added.
Now.
Commit one citizen state and commit an act.
It's in.
Is she in development?
OK, so six Phyliss.
Twenty six inceptions, and you'll see that it has committed to the repository.
Okay, so now let me go back to the repository actually.
And now when you open this project.
You go back to my demo is our project, right?
OK, so now it can guy what does that come name?
Architect Asian Development.
Right.
So there should be a branch here.
I think it's not reflecting.
Oh, we need to push with our push.
How do you expect to see this.
Get my back.
I hope you guys got this.
Okay.
We just committed.
We did not push our brand story.
All right.
So without pushing, I'm going I'm sensing here for the brands, which is very bad.
Okay, so let's push this time.
I have to push the origin back to the developed brands, not to the mast, because I created one brand
and I am pushing that branch to that specific developed brands.
Only if you're right, master.
All your core goes to the master wrench, isn't it?
Now the architect is working on separate brands, which is developed.
So give.
Develop.
So that's why I did initially.
Right Master is what you do by default and you get as it develop.
OK.
And you'll see that Will Brands is recently created.
You recently boosted brands car devil.
OK.
And you can move like from master to develop like this.
So this is a branch of it.
Architects are looking unmastered is about reignition.
That's perfect.
Now let's go back to.
Asian architects have pushed the corps right?
Now it's time to switch to get X is a good X.
Yeah.
OK.
Here is where you are.
American Development Team is sitting.
So here is also one architect who had hired recently and he was asked to continue the work, which are
Asian architect is doing.
So the first step, he will actually pull the cord.
But this time he will say get pull all Jean Knaack Master.
It's devel up.
OK.
He has to pull devil develop.
Or at least we used to go masturbate by default.
But when you are working in branches instead of master.
Make sure you give the brand name which you are invested in.
Here it is.
Autogen, develop it and enter and that's it.
Everything is in your mission.
Now go to this.
Get X off your tips.
It is getting demo right.
Kidding.
Click.
Just click on this.
And it was sure.
OK, you have pulled out but you have not switched brands to that devil.
So right now you are in Master Branch.
How do you switch.
You are a brand from master to develop.
OK.
You have.
You have taken the latest gaud from develop into your mission.
That's fine.
But do you want current brands is pointing to master.
You have to switch it to development.
How to do that.
Simple.
Get take out.
So.
Kate, check out which brands you want to take out develop.
So give that develop.
OK.
You see that switched to a new branch, double up, that's all.
And now you move what it click on this and you'll see it automatically switch to develop.
OK.
So one thing you have to observe carefully.
If you want to create new branch, you have to provide a command.
Go get.
Check out.
Yeah.
You have to add this alphabet hyphen B so that it creates a new branch.
And so we just do it.
But if you want to switch to a new brand which is already created, then you can simply check out.
You can skip this hyphen.
B be OK.
Please remember the difference.
So if you want to create new then only to be used this hyphen B because we already done that.
So the simplest fixed using get checked out.
Come on.
And I just said you would all find it here.
Get checked out.
Get check or hyphen B.
And you know what branch you are in.
And if you're under Dillard branch you'll have to use hyphen D and give that that village the branch.
And if you want to push the scope of the specific branch.
Name.
Bush auditing develop.
OK.
Good.
Now, we have switched to to develop brands of our gate X.
OK.
So here.
You'll see that Mendola Brandon on three test cases.
Rich Asian development team have done.
And here we are seeing all the changes.
So now I'm at a game development team decided to add one more fee here.
Let's assume.
Yeah.
Just add one test.
That's in telling you, OK.
And then again, same stuff.
There is some concept are meant to conflict with tiles.
We're talking the next lecture.
Because that's the only tricky part in it.
What if there is a match?
Conflict happens.
And now you know what?
All this madness get Hubb intelligently doing it bite's loom.
Why take all your ad some time that if God could not understand your MIT concept, it might reject you
a little bit at that time?
We say it doesn't meant conflict at that particular time either.
We ourselves have to go and fix that test by writing the code, by looking oh, about heck.
What is the code present?
Presenting the basehead level.
And what is the court doesn't know what the local mission.
And we have the largest.
It does not do that work for us.
And as I told you, 95 percent of time.
Good.
Does that work for us?
But sometimes that is a probability.
Very good.
Face to match.
So at that time, we have to build that.
Look, I tell you one example in my dumb English, just like how the midst conflict can occur and how
can you fix it.
That being OK.
Just continue on the floor.
So right now we are dealing with masters, which we are going to grab.
So.
OK, so it's quick to stash and then come it's I hope, check if that selenium test is added.
OK, good.
Get Comet.
And development team.
OK.
Then you get Bush ordered in, developed.
Then and now, you'll see for selenium, there are four test cases out are right now.
Go back to your repository, refresh it and you will see.
I'm going to go in development team added a second to go.
OK.
You will clearly see it's fight.
Also, you'll see American Development.
This particular folder, architect, Asian Development, mortified.
These two files, which you can clearly see in there after American Development Team have modified this
file that you want.
They can.
And you can open that and you can see that lastly, OK, for this.
Now, let's assume that with this push, this plant is completely ready.
OK.
So earlier I a door that they'll be working by digging separate branch and they make modification to
that framework instantly.
OK, now let's assume that with this bushwalk, American guy had done an Asian development team.
Already did.
And now this gold is full fledged and it's ready to melt into master.
So that means now a team can use that on their daily basis.
OK.
It's like moving into production.
And we generally don't know how to move and met this mask.
This devilment branch into monster.
OK.
So you know that masteries only day can get a regression test cases.
And this they can get a frame.
But now both are ready.
And now we need to meth's does develop branch into monster and make this as one powerful framework with
all the frame stingiest.
And by architect.
So how to do that?
So for that, first you have to switch to Monster Branch.
Switch to monster transfers.
Get take out
monster.
OK.
And make sure you have the latest court.
You can do that.
Get full origin, master that just making sure that we are having the latest court, which is presenting
good.
Have a repository.
Good.
We are having the up to date court.
Now, if you want to meet Devil Brand once it is completely ready in.
Do you want regular deliverables, Master Branch.
You can simply do that at the gate met which branch you need to meet.
They will operate.
Develop.
OK.
If you like this developed branch, you will be missed in two.
You were active Bletch.
So he and I were active branches master because we just switched to the new branch master.
Right.
And the branch.
What you provide here will be missed into your master.
Same thing.
You will find the command here to get met to met a different branch into your active branch because
there's different brands.
Development is complete.
And now we want willing to mendicant lecture.
OK, so hit and enter.
And you'll see that then develop.
It's actually mess in master.
OK.
So Italy add in master.
We used to have only two test cases.
Right.
But in developed the immediate TADS cases.
And finally for selenium they made for disguises.
And now you'll see as we missed in door master, you will see all those genius in the master as well.
OK.
Where we are now.
Get X.
Get it.
There's nothing better.
This mission.
Yeah.
You'll see that this is a master branch now.
And master runs also.
You are seeing all the updated core whatever are done for development.
So that's why in develop we added one more test.
Right.
You're going to see that here.
And what IBM test.
Open that beam test.
OK, three test cases and arrest EPA test three, test every bit test cases.
OK.
Now, if you want to add one more test, you can do that as the new glass.
Daniel.
I'm just showing the sample, what if you add new test, if you add the new test, it will be first,
as you know, Kushan month and then now you are.
You want to master branches.
I mean, because I would have all the development just OK.
So if you want to add this file you filed against it, get at STOD and that will add the new project,
what you created here.
OK.
They our Java at Q8 Click Academy.
OK, you have done that here, right.
Perfect.
Now get X Master, have everything but get demo mastered.
We have to still pull that right.
So get X.
Let me push that door without quick comments.
We have them get out.
Right.
Get Kermit.
Final coming, because we have done all the tenders and everything finally coming by.
So or get extremely Zevo, it's.
They show the will of many people, then they are actually signing off on this project because they
have missed all the developing D.M. and I have done in the master.
Then I will say get push Autogen the master this time because we are working on a master advance only.
Right.
We have already Mr. Developed Branch and we are pushing out and died cord into Monster.
So it's already done.
Paul Gordon now isn't repository.
So now to the American development team.
So for them now, let me switch to the American label.
See you do da da C.D..
Get there more.
And here right now, I'm in Davila branch.
You can see it here.
You can also know they get branch come.
It says as a devil.
So I will actually do get checked out.
Devil M..
OK.
Once you've checked into the master branch initially, you will have only to test guesses because you
don't have a late escort and there is no demo file also with a simple pull gate full auditing master.
Everything will be in your mission now.
You'll see that and just click on this.
It will actually update stuff for you.
It refers to project.
Yeah, you'll see that.
Then why is up etting now and all the fortified inside information, three files and Selenia, which
should be full?
OK, so that's pretty much about branching.
And now you clearly know how to create their brand, how to work on it.
And once the development is damply, how do Mr. Brands, who do you are on master brands and how you
can do a push and pull with the different people coordinating each of them?
Okay, so that's pretty much I learned this lecture.
And the next lecture will start looking at about Med's conflicts.
Okay.
Thank you.